mytipshub.com 2019-12-03

# Privacy Policy - MyTipsHub

This privacy policy is effective for all the pages, posts and services offered by **MyTipsHub.**

###  **Personal Identification Information**

We may collect personal identification information from users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when users visit our site, fill out an inquiry form or send an email to us. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, phone number, mobile number, address etc. Users may also be asked for their email address in order to subscribe to Email Newsletter. Users may, however, visit our site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from users only if they willingly submit such information to us for contacting us, commenting on this weblog, fills a form or in any other way. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

###  **Non-Personal Information**

We may collect non-personal identification information about users whenever they interact with our website. Non-personal identification information may include but not limited to, Browser, OS, Device, Display Resolution, IP, Language, Country, City, Demographic, Information,  Time Spent on Website, ISP and other similar information.

###  **Web Browser Cookies**

Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance user experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent.

####  **Data Collection through Third Parties**

We may also use Third Party Programs, Codes, Plugins, Cookies and Software to collect users’ general data. However we will not collect users’ personal data without his consent. We may use Google Analytics, Stats Counters and other such services for this purpose.

###  **How we use Collected Information**

This website may collect and use users personal information for the following purposes:

To Improve Customer Service (We may use your personal information to contact you and respond to your questions, requests, suggestions and complaints).

###  **Sharing your Personal Information**

We do not sell or otherwise share your personal identification information to others for commercial purpose. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

We may also share your information to trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

###  **Third party Advertisements and Links**

Users may find advertising, website links, affiliate links or other content on this website that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

Ads appearing on this website may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

###  **Google AdSense**

This website also served ads by Google. We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick.  Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our website and other sites on the Internet. DART uses “non personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc.

You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/

###  **Changes to this  Privacy Policy**

Admin of **www.mytipshub.com** has the discretion to update, revise or change this privacy policy at any time. When we do, updated privacy policy will be available on this webpage and will also revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

###  **Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this Website, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

 **Late Update: 01-11-2019**
